freegamesway.com 2019-01-17

# Privacy Policy

## MyPlayCity ® Online Privacy Policy

### INTRODUCTION

PLEASE READ THIS DOCUMENT CAREFULLY. IT CONTAINS IMPORTANT INFORMATION THAT YOU SHOULD KNOW BEFORE CONTINUING TO USE OUR SERVICES OR PRODUCTS (AS SUCH TERM DEFINED IN THE TERMS OF USE). BY CONTINUING TO USE MYPLAYCITY SOFTWARE AND SERVICES YOU WILL BE DEEMED TO HAVE ACCEPTED THIS MYPLAYCITY'S PRIVACY POLICY.

Your use of the MyPlayCity Services and Software provided herein, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and MyPlayCity's Terms of Use <http://www.myplaycity.com/terms_of_use/> . By using MyPlayCity's Website (as such term defined below), Services or Products (such as video games available through the Website), you are accepting the practices set out in this Privacy Policy and those Terms of Use. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date below to determine if the policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of the MyPlayCity's Website, Services or software following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

This privacy statement was last updated on **May 20, 2018**. MyPlayCity, Inc. and its affiliates (collectively, " _ **MyPlayCity**_ ") has created this privacy statement in order to disclose its information gathering and dissemination practices for its Services, Product and various websites under MyPlayCity's control (collectively, the " _ **Website**_ ").

A note about Website: While Website may be deemed to be a U.S. website, however, some of our Services, data centers, service providers, affiliates or operating partners and servers may be located in other countries. As such, our Products and Services may be subject to the laws of numerous countries and jurisdictions, some of which may require us to disclose certain information about our users. We are committed to keeping your information private, while still following all applicable laws.

If you have any concerns or feel that there are certain problems or issues relating to compliance with the policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, please submit a report by emailing at: <http://www.myplaycity.com/support>.

### Word from MyPlayCity

MyPlayCity has a strong commitment to providing superior service to all of our customers and visitors of this Website and particularly respecting your concerns about privacy. We understand that you may have questions about how this Website collects and uses information and we have prepared this statement to inform you of the privacy principles that govern the Website (the " _ **Privacy Policy**_ "). We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information or a list of our customers to third parties. However, as described in more detail below, there are limited circumstances in which some of your information will be shared with third parties, under strict restrictions, so it is important for you to review this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy contains numerous general and technical details about the steps we take to respect your privacy concerns. We have organized this Privacy Policy by major processes and areas so that you can quickly link to the information of most interest to you. The bottom line is that meeting your needs and expectations form the foundation of everything we do - including protecting your privacy.

### Changes in Privacy Policy

We want you to always be aware of what personal and other information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it. All personal information that we collect will be handled according to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time the information is collected. If the Privacy Policy changes in any significant respect, we will not use your personal data in a manner that is inconsistent with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time your information was collected without your permission.

From time to time, we may find the need to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check the Privacy Policy published on this Website regularly to ensure that you are aware of all terms governing your use of this Website.

### Third Party Websites and Applications

Not all content on our Website is owned and controlled by us. The Website may contain links to websites owned and/or operated by third parties. **These third** parties may drop cookies and/or use web beacons on your system, which may be used to identify your preferences or to recognize if you have previously had contact with these third parties. We do not control these websites, their content, or their information collection practices and are not responsible for their privacy policies or practices. Please direct all concerns regarding any third party website to that site's administrator or webmaster.

We may use third party advertising companies to display advertisements when you visit the Website. These companies may use general information about your visits to the Website as well as other websites to provide specialized advertisements tailored to you. If you would like more information about this practice, please direct such concerns to the advertising company's administrator or webmaster.

We may also make third party applications available through our Website or our Products and Services. Please note that when you enable a third party application, any the information collected by us is processed under this Privacy Policy while any information collected by the third parties is governed by their respective privacy policy.

**Affiliate Programs**

MyPlayCity may also participate in a third party affiliate programs utilizing its Products, services and Website (" _ **Affiliate Programs**_ "). Most of these Affiliate Programs work seamlessly with the MyPlayCity's Products and do not effect or interfere with your operation of Website, Products and/or Services or your user-experience, at the same time, essentially enabling MyPlayCity to be credited for the results of your searches and user-activity on the Website. MyPlayCity's participation in the Affiliate Programs enables MyPlayCity to enhance your enjoyment of Website, Products and/or Services, while allowing MyPlayCity to provide you with high quality free content that you can enjoy while visiting our Website and using our Products and Services. Please note however that such Affiliate Programs are not under MyPlayCity's control and subject to the applicable licenses, privacy policies and terms and conditions.

### COLLECTED INFORMATION

### Browsing

This Website does not collect personally identifiable information from your computer when you browse the Website and request pages from our servers. This means that, unless you voluntarily and knowingly provide us with personally identifiable information, we will not know your name, your e-mail address, or any other personally identifiable information. When you request a page from our Website, our servers log the information provided in the HTTP request header, JavaScript or similar technical tools, including the IP number, the time of the request, the URL of your request and other information. We collect such information in order to make our Website function correctly and provide you the functionality that you see on this Website, as our servers use this information to deliver to you the pages on this Website. We also use this information to better understand how visitors use our Website and how we can better tune our Website, its contents and functionality to meet your needs.

### Information We Collect

As a visitor to this Website, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information as described above in Section Browsing above. In connection with other activities, such as utilizing online software applications or downloading any of the Products and Services available on the Website, MyPlayCity may ask you to voluntarily supply us with certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, MyPlayCity may ask that you provide us personal information, defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains.

MyPlayCity is the sole owner of the information it gathers on the Website.  MyPlayCity will only share your information with outside parties in ways that are described in this privacy statement or if we are required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, cooperate with law enforcement agencies, or comply with a legal process served on our Website and the subsequent legislation adopted in the United States.

When you use the Website, MyPlayCity or third parties authorized by MyPlayCity may also collect certain technical and routing information about your computer to facilitate your use of the Website and its Products and Services. When you surf the Internet, your Internet browser (such as Mozilla Firefox or Microsoft Internet Explorer) automatically transmits some information to MyPlayCity every time you access content on one of our internet domains within the Website. Examples of such information include the URL of the Web page you were just on (known as the " _ **Refer**_ "), the IP (or Internet Protocol) address of the computer you are using, or the browser version you are using to access our site. All of this information may be collected by MyPlayCity and used to help improve our offerings to you.

We use such data to facilitate and track your use of the Website and its Products and Services. MyPlayCity also uses such environmental variables to measure traffic patterns on the Website. Without expressly informing you in each particular circumstance, we do not match such information with any of your personal information.

MyPlayCity may establish relationships with various service providers whose services may become available to you from this Website or from other websites that are linked to this Website. Typically, these providers would offer services that MyPlayCity customers might find useful, such as those that can be used in conjunction with MyPlayCity Services and Products. In order to use those Services, you may be required to provide personal information to the providers. Unless expressly provided to the contrary, personal information that you provide while you are visiting a provider's Website will be subject to the privacy policy posted on such site, and personal information that you provide while on this Website in conjunction with a provider's service will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

### Information Relating to Children

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) was passed by the U.S. Congress in November 1998. COPPA provides parents with specific rights regarding their children's privacy. For additional information and resources on COPPA, please visit the Federal Trade Commission Web site at <http://www.ftc.gov/>. The MyPlayCity Website and any Products or Services available on that site are not directed at children under 13 years of age and, therefore, COPPA does not apply.

### Securing the Transmission and Storage of Information

MyPlayCity operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our users. MyPlayCity takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online Products or Services, and you use these Products and Services at your own risk.

### C. USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

### How your personal information is used

MyPlayCity collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select.

MyPlayCity may collect information about the use of the Website, such as the types of Services used and how many users we receive daily. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually. MyPlayCity may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes.

MyPlayCity recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on this Website. Without your consent, MyPlayCity will not communicate any information to you regarding Products, Services, and special offers available from MyPlayCity or its affiliates, although we may find it necessary to communicate with you regarding your use of the Services on this Website. Except in the particular circumstances described in this Privacy Policy, MyPlayCity will also not provide your name to other companies or organizations without your consent.

### Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

Although we will always strive to guard your identity, we may disclose your personally identifiable information without your permission in limited circumstances. We will only do so if we have a good-faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (1) comply with laws, regulations, or government requests or (2) to investigate or protect against harmful activities to our guests, visitors, associates, or property (including the Website), or to others. If we are required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide your personally identifiable information, we will only do so upon receipt of appropriate documentation. We may also disclose your information to investigate violation of and enforce our Terms of Use. Please know that we do not take this responsibility lightly. Your privacy is of paramount importance to us.

### Choices available to you

You can always choose whether or not to disclose personally identifiable information and that choice will not prevent you from using the MyPlayCity Website. Please note, however, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with some of the Services dependent upon the collection of this information and you will be given an opportunity to "opt-in" and make your preference choices for any items that are optional and which are not prerequisite for our rendering such Services.

### Cookies

Our Website uses "cookie" technology. "Cookies" are short pieces of data generated by a web server that a website stores on a user's computer. Certain pages on our Website may require the use of a cookie for purposes of keeping information you enter on multiple pages together. Cookies also enable us to customize our Website and offerings to your needs and provide you with a better online experience with us. You may set your browser to block cookies (consult the instructions for your particular browser on how to do this), although doing so may adversely affect your ability to perform certain transactions, use certain functionality and access certain content on our Website.

### D. PRIVACY-RELATED INQUIRIES AND COMPLAINTS

MyPlayCity takes and addresses its users' privacy concerns with utmost respect and attention. If you believe that there was an instance of non-compliance with this Online Privacy Policy with regard to your personal information or you have other related inquiries or concerns, you may write or contact MyPlayCity at email: <http://www.myplaycity.com/support>.

Copyright © 2018 MyPlayCity, Inc. All rights reserved. This Website and accompanying Products and documentation are the copyrighted property of MyPlayCity, Inc. and/or its licensors and protected by copyright laws and international intellectual property treaties. MyPlayCity and related logo, and all related Product and service names, design marks and slogans are the trademarks and/or registered trademarks of MyPlayCity, Inc. or its affiliates. All other Product and service marks contained herein are the trademarks of their respective owners. Any use of the MyPlayCity or third party trademarks or logos without the prior written consent of MyPlayCity, Inc. or the applicable trademark owner is strictly prohibited.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

© MyPlayCity Inc  
901 N. Pitt St.  
Suite 325  
Alexandria, VA 22314, USA  
Contact us  
All trademarks are the property of their respective owners. All Rights Reserved.
